revelup.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy | Revel Systems iPad POS

## Revel Systems, Inc. Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: May 24, 2018**

This Privacy Policy applies to all products and services offered by Revel Systems, Inc., and our affiliates (collectively “Revel”, “we”, “us” or “our”), including our websites, products, services, mobile and software applications we own or control (the “Services”).

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to products or services offered by other companies or individuals, such as ** ** payment processing services, hardware, third-party software, or ISP services that customers may use in connection with the Services, including such third-party products or services that a customer may lease or procure through Revel. **  **Our Privacy Policy also does not apply to data that we process as a service provider on behalf of our customers, as our handling of this data is governed by the contract with our customer.

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it and what we do with it.

### HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION

### INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE

We collect information you provide when you access or participate in certain aspects of our Services, such as when you create any type of account, use our Services, make purchases, leave a review, download one of our mobile applications, complete a survey, or enter contests or other promotions. The information you provide may specifically identify you (“Personal Information”), and includes: your name, email address, postal mailing address, business address, and telephone numbers. We also may use a third-party payment service to collect payment information to process your transactions with us. The amount and type of information you provide depends on the nature of the interaction. We may need to collect and process these types of Personal Information in order to provide requested services to you, or because we are legally required to do so. You may always refuse to supply Personal Information, with the caveat that it may prevent you from using our corresponding Services.

We may receive your Personal Information from other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, social media platforms (including from people with whom you are friends or otherwise connected) and from other third parties.

### INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED BY USING OR ACCESSING OUR SERVICES

When you access, use or interact with our Services, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Revel may also collect Personal Information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.

### COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s devices. We use cookies and similar technologies (such as pixel tags) to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our Services, and their preferences. Revel visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their devices should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our Services, with the drawback that certain features of our Services may not be available or may not function properly without the aid of cookies. We do not currently respond to browser do-not-track signals.

We use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of the Services and report on activities and trends.  This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps and online resources.  You can learn about Google’s practices by going to www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/, and exercise the opt out provided by Google by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

### DEVICE INFORMATION AND IDENTIFIERS

When you use our Services, including but not limited to when you install software, download any type of Services or access the Services, on your computer, tablet, mobile device or any other devices, we collect device-specific identifiers and mobile network information including phone number, device type, device identifier and operating system. We may also request access to certain rights on your devices, such as access to storage or camera, and ability to send push notifications.

### OTHER INFORMATION

We may also collect other information that does not identify or relate to an identified or identifiable individual, such as browser and device information, demographic and other information that does not reveal the individual’s specific identity, and information that has been aggregated in a manner that it no longer reveals an individual’s specific identity.  We may use and disclose such information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law.

### How We Use and Retain Information

We use Personal Information for our legitimate business purposes, including to provide, maintain, use, protect and improve our Services, and to develop new products and services. For example, we use Personal Information:

  * To respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, complete your transactions, and provide you with related customer service. We will engage in these activities to manage our contractual relationship with you and/or to comply with a legal obligation.
  * To send administrative information to you, such as changes to our terms, conditions and policies, as well as marketing communications that we believe may be of interest. We will engage in this activity with your consent or where we have a legitimate interest.
  * To personalize your experience on the Site by presenting products and offers tailored to you, and to facilitate social sharing functionality. We will provide personalized services either with your consent or because we have a legitimate interest.
  * To allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions and to administer these activities. Some of these activities have additional rules containing information about how we use and disclose your Personal Information.  We use this information to manage our contractual relationship with you.
  * For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns, and operating and expanding our business activities. We engage in these activities to manage our contractual relationship with you, to comply with a legal obligation, and/or because we have a legitimate interest.

We retain Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.  The criteria used to determine our retention periods include:  (i) the length of time we have an ongoing relationship with you and provide the Services to you; (ii) whether there is a legal obligation to which we are subject; or (iii) whether retention is advisable in light of our legal position (such as in regard to applicable statutes of limitations, litigation or regulatory investigations).

### Your Personal Information may be disclosed:

  * To our affiliates: Revel Australia Pty., Limited, Revel Systems (UK) Limited, Revel Systems (GB) Limited, Revel Commercial Holdings Limited, Revel Systems Global, PTE. LTD., Revel Systems Canada, ULC, Revel Systems, UAB, Revel Systems Poland sp. z o.o, mStream POS, Inc., Best of Bees, Inc., for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.
  * To our third party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email delivery, auditing and other services.
  * To third party companies that provide services you have requested, such as payment processing services that you use in connection with the Services.

### AGGREGATED STATISTICS

We may collect statistics about the use of our Services. In addition, we share anonymous information, including aggregated information, and share such anonymous information with third parties, and we may also share such anonymous information publicly to provide information about the general use of our Services.

### ADDITIONAL USES AND DISCLOSURES

We may also use and disclose your Personal Information as we believe to be necessary or appropriate, especially when we have a legal obligation or legitimate interest to do so: (a) to comply with applicable law, which may include laws outside your country of residence, to respond to requests from public and government authorities, which may include authorities outside your country of residence, to cooperate with law enforcement, or for other legal reasons; (b) to enforce our terms and conditions; and (c) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others.

### THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements regarding goods and services that may be of interest to you when you access and use the Services and other websites or online services, based on information relating to your access to and use of the Services and other websites or online services on any of your devices, as well as on information received from third parties.  To do so, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through the use of pixel tags).  They may also use these technologies, along with information they collect about your online use, to recognize you across the devices you use, such as a mobile phone and a laptop.  If you would like more information about this practice, and to learn how to opt out of it in desktop and mobile browsers on the particular device on which you are accessing this Privacy Policy, please visit <http://optout.aboutads.info/#/> and <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/>.

### SECURITY

We seek to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within our organization.  Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately notify us in accordance with the “Contact Us” section below.

### REGISTRATION VIA THIRD PARTY ACCOUNTS AND SOCIAL MEDIA SHARING

You may be given the opportunity to register with us or use our Services via third party accounts such as Google, Apple or Facebook. These services will authenticate your identity and may provide you the option to share certain information (such as your name and email address) with us. We may store the information you provide us through such accounts and combine it with other information, including Personal Information. Disabling your Facebook or other such account may not terminate your relationship with us.

Our Services may also include social media features, such as sharing widgets provided by Facebook, Twitter, Google and Pinterest. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting within our Services, and may set cookies. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly within our Services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

### ACCESSING AND UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you would like to request to review, correct, update, suppress, restrict or delete Personal Information that you have previously provided to us, object to the processing of Personal Information, or if you would like to request to receive an electronic copy of your Personal Information for purposes of transmitting it to another company (to the extent this right to data portability is provided to you by applicable law), you may contact us by using the contact details in the “Contacting Us” section below.  We will respond to your request consistent with applicable law.

** ** In your request, please make clear what Personal Information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have your Personal Information suppressed from our database or otherwise let us know what limitations you would like to put on our use of your Personal Information.  For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request.  We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting a change or deletion (e.g., when you make a purchase or enter a promotion, you may not be able to change or delete the Personal Information provided until after the completion of such purchase or promotion). **  **There may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed.

### CHOICES

If you no longer want to receive marketing-related emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out by contacting us in accordance with the “Contact Us” section below or by using the opt-out mechanism contained in each such email.  We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable.  Please note that if you opt-out of receiving marketing-related emails from us, we may still send you important administrative messages, from which you cannot opt-out.

### BUSINESS TRANSFERS

If Revel, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Revel goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, we have a legitimate interest in disclosing or transferring user information to a third party in connection with such a transaction.

### CROSS-BORDER TRANSFERS

Revel is a global organization and your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers.  By using the Services you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have data protection rules that are different from those of your country.

Additional information regarding the EEA:  Some of these non-EEA countries are recognized by the European Commission as providing an adequate level of data protection according to EEA standards (the full list of these countries is available here: <https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/adequacy-protection-personal-data-non-eu-countries_en>. For transfers from the EEA to countries not considered adequate by the European Commission, we have put in place adequate measures, such as standard contractual clauses adopted by the European Commission to protect your Personal Information. You may obtain a copy of these measures by contacting us in accordance with the “Contacting Us” section below.

### PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. If we make changes, we will notify you by posting the updated policy on this page and revising the “Last Updated” date above. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of any Services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. This Privacy Policy covers our practices, and does not cover the practices of unaffiliated third parties.

### CONTACTING US

Any questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to Revel Systems, Inc. at **[mailto:privacy@revelsystems.com](mailto:privacy@revelsystems.com)** or 303 Second Street, North Tower, Suite 550 San Francisco, CA 94107.

_Additional Information regarding the EEA_ :

You also may:

  * Contact our data protection officer at [dpo@revelsystems.com](mailto:dpo@revelsystems.com) with any questions about this Privacy Policy.
  * Lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority competent for your country or region.
